allsingaporestuff.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | All Singapore Stuff - Real Singapore News

By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions, together the Website Conditions. If you do not consent to these conditions, please leave the site and cease use of the website and related services immediately.

This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected by AllSingaporeStuff.com and/or its related entities, affiliates and subsidiaries. This, along with the Website Terms and Conditions makes up the 'Website Conditions' which you agree to be bound by through the use of our website. 

For the purpose of this Policy, “we” and “our” shall refer to AllSingaporeStuff.com.

1\. When is information collected from you?

1.1 When you register for or use any of our services on websites owned and/or operated by us.

1.2 When you take part in any contest, survey or promotion conducted by us and/or our business partners.

1.3 When you register as a member of websites owned and/or operated by us, or hosted by us on behalf of our business partners or use services on such websites.

2\. What is the information used for?

2.1 Information which you provide to us may be used and disclosed by us and our affiliates, business partners and contractors (who may be based outside Singapore) for the following purposes:

2.1.1 to respond to your requests and queries;

2.1.2 to provide goods and services to you;

2.1.3 to verify and process your personal particulars and payments;

2.1.4 to communicate with you;

2.1.5 to enforce contractual and legal rights and obligations;

2.1.6 for marketing research, user profile and statistical analysis;

2.1.7 to send you information, promotions, updates, and marketing and advertising materials in relation to our goods and services and those of third party organisations;

2.1.8 complying with law, the requests of law enforcement and regulatory officials, or orders of court; and

2.1.9 for any other purposes for which we have obtained your consent, including during the registration process.

2.2 In the event that you participate in contests or other promotional programs on our websites sponsored or organized by third parties or purchase goods and services offered by third parties or offer goods and services to third parties on our sites, your information may be disclosed to and used by such third parties.

2.3 We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

2.4 We will release your information only if we are compelled to do so under a court order such as a subpeona and the release of such information is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

3\. Use of cookies

3.1 AllSingaporeStuff.com uses "cookies", where a small data file is sent to your browser to store and track information about you when you enter our websites. The cookie is used to track information such as the number of users and their frequency of use, profiles of users and their preferred sites.

3.2 Like many web site operators, AllSingaporeStuff.com may use an independent company to measure and analyse the Internet usage across our web sites. AllSingaporeStuff.com uses such services to collect the following core information on the usage of our web sites, including:

3.2.1 The number of page views (or page impressions) that occur on AllSingaporeStuff.com web sites;

3.2.2 The number of unique visitors to AllSingaporeStuff.com

3.2.3 How long these unique visitors (on average) spend on AllSingaporeStuff.com when they do visit; and

3.2.4 Common entry and exit points into AllSingaporeStuff.com.

3.3 This information is collated by the Third Parties and provided to AllSingaporeStuff.com to assist in analysing the usage of web sites. Such data is also accessible by media organizations and research companies, for the purpose of conducting industry comparisons with other Internet portals.

3.4 Pages on AllSingaporeStuff.com web sites may be coded with software which enables the Third Party Market Research Companies and AllSingaporeStuff.com to track visitors to our web sites.

4\. Online Privacy Policy Only

4.1 This privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

5\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

5.1 AllSingaporeStuff.com reserves the right to change, without prior notice or liability, these policies by updating this page with the new policies. 

6\. Contacting Us

6.1 If you have any problems or questions regarding this privacy policy, all enquiries may be directed to AllSingaporeStuff.com Admin Team by clicking on "Contact Us".
